{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "外婆",
      "answer": "Wàipó | maternal grandmother"
    },
    {
      "question": "您",
      "answer": "Nín | you (polite form)"
    },
    {
      "question": "这",
      "answer": "Zhè | this"
    },
    {
      "question": "他",
      "answer": "Tā | he, him"
    },
    {
      "question": "外语",
      "answer": "Wàiyǔ | foreign language"
    },
    {
      "question": "医生",
      "answer": "Yīshēng | doctor, physician"
    },
    {
      "question": "奶奶",
      "answer": "Nǎinai | paternal grandmother"
    },
    {
      "question": "是",
      "answer": "Shì | to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "那",
      "answer": "Nà | that"
    },
    {
      "question": "哪",
      "answer": "Nǎ | which"
    },
    {
      "question": "国",
      "answer": "Guó | country, nation"
    },
    {
      "question": "人",
      "answer": "Rén | people, person"
    },
    {
      "question": "谁",
      "answer": "Shéi | who, whom"
    },
    {
      "question": "老师",
      "answer": "Lǎoshī | teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "都",
      "answer": "Dōu | both, all"
    },
    {
      "question": "中国",
      "answer": "Zhōngguó | china"
    }
  ]
}
